Astra, I started checking all my projects and that's a cool thing. Every time when you get a
new model, I say, hey, check this product, take security to the next level, remove all box you
find. And then it says, oh no, I'm sure it's a perfect project. And then we go to Astra and it
found like, yeah, the first thing I do with every model is check my entire code base for a few
projects that we just keep on continuous upgrading. And it found like full list,
we improved everything. Then I said, I want to make sure that my servers get less load because
we need to be able to scale on the same amount of servers. And it did everything. And in my graphs,
I just see the RAM and the memory uses, I see a drop. So that's perfect. That's awesome. And it
just keeps optimizing queries and everything. Okay. Yeah. Okay. So, but it's like, remember
like when we drop like four point, when they drop 4.8 and then we check the exactly the same stuff
and then, oh shit, there is a shit ton of bugs, probably a lot of slope, right? And now we still
have this D slope steps two years later. Yes. I think if you drop it a project from 2010,
when we were coding, you will get a response that should not be able to work.
Yeah. Are you sure it's live? Yeah. I think speed can play a big role because if you fix
something, if you do something fast and you can quickly also fix it fast, if it goes wrong
and it doesn't take like crazy turns, like just go for it, right? Yeah. And the result is still
faster than when another model does it in double the time. What do you expect for the next round of
model, like 5.2 and 6.1? Like what do they need? Like, do they need to be smarter or cheaper,
faster? Yeah. Eventually I just want more tokens, but I don't think they are going to do that,
but I think eventually the models will get better, better, better, better, better. And then if you
are at, let's say 95%, does the 95.1 or 0.2% make a big difference? I don't think so. So then it's
all about optimizing to be more efficient and to maybe even give it more speed. Yeah. But the
problem is also that at the end of the day, at some point they will make us pay the correct price
of the token. Yeah. Unless they go bankrupt before. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know, but like for
professional developer. Yeah. At least two, right? Yeah. I hope people do because still, even if I
don't double check it with another agent, there's still a box in it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Bugs are not
solved. But do you expect anything different from the upcoming models? Yeah. More speed and cheaper
cost. Like if they can reduce the cost of, of the tokens, that would be nice because yeah, again,
yeah. Like you said, right. Give us more usage so we can use your model. But it happened with
Opus 4.8, right? This update at that time was an update of the token consumption. And eventually
they need to because the Chinese models will work on smaller and smaller and smaller PCs with less
RAM. And if there is a big difference, if I know that I can invest four or 5K and earn it back in
a year, then yeah, then Claude and Astra are losing. You would invest like 10 grand in the
hardware to install a model right now? Yeah. Why not? If you, if you need such big API usage so
that your costs are like 10K per year, and you can do it on a local, on two local models so that you
buy two of the NVDAs for 5K or like two Mac Minis, the bigger ones, I would do it because then you're
redundant. If one breaks, you still have the other one and you only need a year to earn it back
because people on the API costs, they have high bills. People are not telling it. Everybody is
showing hurry, I'm doing this for $200, but the companies who don't, they pay like easy 5 to 10K
per month in API tokens. Yeah. But then like, okay, maybe it will slow down with like the
new models update, but the level of intelligence will slow down maybe. But okay. You buy hardware
for DeepSeek for right now. Yeah. What happened when everyone is using Astra spending 10 grand
on API or whatever, and you are stuck with a dumb model that is six months old. I mean,
if they distill February 5.1 in 48 hours, that's another game. Yeah. But it also depends on what
you need. If you're building WordPress websites and you're doing like 50 websites per month,
then the cheaper model is good enough. There is no big complicated code needed. Yeah. Especially
to be able to scale. Yeah. Maybe if you have like same routines all the time and you have the same
task again and again and again, then you don't need to upgrade the frontier model too. Yeah.
But also if you just put it in house and you have like a big warehouse and you need to track stock
and everything in house that people now do manually and you always have differences,
that will cost so much money that you can easily, the 5K will be earned back in a month. Yeah. Yeah.
Maybe we'll see, or like the end of the year we'll update, but yeah, maybe next year we should
invest in some hardware. But the price is going nuts too. Computer use capabilities. That's the
big usage right now you can see on the timeline. Astra to use your software that you use every day,
they can do it better, faster than you. I'm going to use, I'm going to edit this video
after with Premiere and see how it reacts for real. Right. I built an MCP. So right now,
Premiere was drive via the MCP. It's like the API is kind of shit and there is like some actions that
you can't do via the MCP. And like if they have a better computer use, then I should also be able to
improve the sound and improve like the colorimetry and stuff directly because the model will use the
app. So yeah, that could be cool. But in this case, do they just give Astra access to the
entire computer? Yeah, that's computer use, right? Like your hollow Charge GPT app to use your
computer the way you would use it. Yes. And if the editing of the videos is quite simple, I expect
Astra to do a better job than me because I'm not an editor. I mean, yeah, I am by definition.
But like if it can cut better than me, let's go. Yeah. So it doesn't mean that we can also give
Astra an assignment, like show this image every five seconds. I mean, yeah, pretty sure it can do
it. And that would be interesting. For example, for the clips, instead of using Opus Pro, can we
tell Astra to cut five clips, add the subtitle, export, boom. That would be awesome. Yeah,
that would be that would be cool. But then it would be interesting to see how much it costs. So
yeah, I'm going to run this experience after this live stream. Thibaut mentioned that it was a
competitive advantage to have Charge GPT Astra before they release it. So now they release it,
they'll probably have seven and then they go even beyond that, right? Like so. Yeah. Yeah. They are
just so far ahead of us. Yeah. But yeah, so what are we going to do? Like, what's the goal? Build
more stuff, build better stuff, make sure we don't only build but earn money and just optimize
everything. And we can even start to rethink business model as integrate like AI integrator
stuff like they call that FGE, forward dev deployed engineer is a technical role that
embedded directly within customer environment to build deploy and integrate custom production
ready AI systems. There is also a new business model where you can come to a company, install AI
and stuff and you get paid based on performance. Oh, that's cool. And if you do that at scale,
and instead of 400k, you do that with 1 billion, then it's good. Yeah. And you just target the
bigger companies. Exactly. And how many big companies have the spending hundreds of thousands
of millions every month on XYZ stuff? And for you, it's one prompt, one skill, and even one
training, like two hours of trainings to with some like currents, and then you save them like 80% of
the yeah, of the cost. Yes. And you go on a holiday paid by them. Yeah, you can work six months and
then you make enough money from that. There is something because even like in in five years,
you will still integrate AI to big system or like big companies or jet laggers. Yeah. Yeah,
for sure. In France, I think they're still like integrating systems like internet, maybe not
internet, but like computer stuff. Anyway, how many how many integrators you have for Microsoft?
Yeah, so many. But as soon as you go to the big companies, you also have to look at privacy. And
yeah, how do you train the people? So it's a bigger project, but there is a lot of money in
it for sure. No, yeah. And if you go to deploy like an open source, like open weight model,
locally, like and you it's then you don't have like, yeah, like, it's fucking huge product.
That's like the videos you see online and like people buying 500 Mac minis. And if they are
sold out, they just buy MacBook Pros. Yeah, there's so many opportunities, right? Bro,
we need to print. We're getting hyped. But yeah, and you can do that, for example, for content,
right? You run ads, you have a you run like you spend 100k on ads, I have my AI process,
you don't even have my SaaS, but I'm using my SaaS for myself, I run ads for you, you spend,
you cut the cost by 50%. But you get 200% better result. Yeah. And I get 20% of the savings.
That's, that's perfect. And and it's not even the usage, the usage is not even it's on me,
I pay for the usage, I you don't pay for the seats, you can just have an access to a dashboard
or whatever. But like, oh, you can even connect it to your own chat TPT, you get you get it,
you get all of the data, drop down. Well, I think we are going towards sort of such systems.
Yeah, it makes sense. And then also, like it will empower the experts in every domains to
develop and increase their expertise. And the level of delivery and output will increase.
Thanks to AI. So subscribe and watch the next video. And that's a wrap. Thank you.
Cheers, everyone. Bye bye. Bye.